[The Epoch of Miyu]
[미유시대]
[Episode 13]
[13화]
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
please wait a moment.
잠시만 기다려 주십시오.
This is the money I borrowed from you last time.
이것은 돈이다 지난번에 당신한테 빌렸어요.
There's no need to rush to pay me back.
갚으려고 서두르실 필요 없어요.
Please take it.
가져가세요.
Otherwise, I'll feel bad.
그렇지 않으면 기분이 나빠질 것입니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Is there anything else?
다른 것이 있나요?
Have the linens in the room been changed?
객실의 린넨은 교체되었나요?
Yes, they have.
예, 그렇습니다.
What did the guest say?
손님이 뭐라고 하셨어요?
No negative feedback for now.
현재로서는 부정적인 피드백이 없습니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Go back to your work.
직장으로 돌아가세요.
You're getting off work soon too.
너도 곧 퇴근이구나.
Yunhai Cotton Textile Factory
운해면방직공장
is a solid partner.
든든한 파트너입니다.
This time, the PR crisis
이번에는 PR 위기
was handled smoothly in the end.
결국 원활하게 처리되었습니다.
Thanks to you.
당신 덕분입니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
No problem.
괜찮아요.
What about the linens
린넨은 어떻습니까
you ordered from abroad?
해외에서 주문하셨나요?
They are also in storage.
그것들도 보관되어 있습니다.
Shanghai is humid,
상하이는 습해요
so it's always right to have an extra set.
그래서 여분의 세트를 갖는 것이 항상 옳습니다.
How come you know so much about linens?
리넨에 대해 어떻게 그렇게 많이 알고 계시나요?
Shouldn't I know about them?
내가 그들에 대해 알아야 하지 않나요?
That's not what I meant.
내 말은 그런 뜻이 아니었어.
I used to work at Purong Hotel
저는 푸롱 호텔에서 일했어요
as an attendant for many years.
수년 동안 수행원으로.
I've experienced
나는 경험했어요
all the work you've done
네가 한 모든 일
and the mistakes you've made.
그리고 당신이 저지른 실수.
No wonder.
당연합니다.
No wonder what?
당연하지, 뭐?
No wonder
당연하지
you can always find so many faults with me.
넌 언제나 찾을 수 있어 나한테 잘못이 너무 많아.
I can't help it.
나는 그것을 도울 수 없다.
It's your first time being a forewoman.
당신이 여주인공이 되는 건 처음이에요.
And it's my first time officially being a general manager.
그리고 공식적으로는 처음이에요 총지배인이 되는 것.
Let's help each other
서로 도와주세요
and bear with each other.
그리고 서로 참아라.
Actually, what I want to do is very simple.
사실 내가 하고 싶은 일은 매우 간단합니다.
I just want to be a good forewoman.
나는 단지 좋은 감독이 되고 싶을 뿐이다.
But...
하지만...
But what?
하지만 뭐?
But we got through
하지만 우리는 해냈어
this crisis together
이 위기를 함께
as a whole executive floor.
전체 임원 층으로.
But I was the only one who got the bonus.
그런데 보너스를 받은 사람은 나뿐이었다.
Everyone thinks I got it through connections.
다들 내가 해냈다고 생각해 연결을 통해.
What do you think then?
그러면 어떻게 생각하세요?
If you think I gave you that bonus
내가 너한테 보너스를 줬다고 생각한다면
because I've lost my mind
내가 정신을 잃었으니까
or was playing favorites,
아니면 즐겨찾기를 재생하고 있었나요?
and you really don't want it,
그런데 넌 정말 그걸 원하지 않는구나,
you can return it to the hotel.
호텔에 반납하시면 됩니다.
If you had the guts to play favorites,
좋아하는 게임을 플레이할 용기가 있다면
I wouldn't dare to receive it, okay?
감히 받을 수가 없겠죠?
You really are quite different.
당신은 정말 다릅니다.
Others bully the weak and fear the strong,
다른 사람들은 약한 사람을 괴롭히고 강한 사람을 두려워합니다.
but you do the exact opposite.
하지만 당신은 정반대로 행동합니다.
If you used this momentum
이 추진력을 사용했다면
to manage your subordinates, it would be great.
부하직원을 관리하기 위해 정말 좋을 것 같아요.
Look at you.
당신을보세요.
You act like being a forewoman is accumulating karma.
넌 마치 집주인처럼 행동해 카르마를 축적하고 있습니다.
You are everywhere—
당신은 어디에나 있습니다—
working overtime,
초과 근무를 하고 있어
covering shifts,
교대근무를 담당하고
taking extra duty…
추가 임무를 수행 중...
You don't seriously think the executive floor
당신은 심각하게 생각하지 않습니다 임원층
can keep everything running smoothly
모든 일이 원활하게 진행되도록 할 수 있어
just by this kind of unconditional self-sacrifice, do you?
그냥 이런 식으로 무조건적인 자기 희생이죠?
I know.
알아요.
Sometimes I want to be tough too.
가끔은 나도 터프해지고 싶을 때가 있다.
But if they don't respect me from the bottom of their hearts,
하지만 그들이 나를 존중하지 않는다면 진심으로
my toughness is just a bluff.
내 강인함은 단지 허세일 뿐이다.
I just want to use my own ability
난 그냥 내 능력을 사용하고 싶을 뿐이야
to prove that I deserve to be in this position.
내가 그럴 자격이 있다는 걸 증명하기 위해 이 위치에 있기 위해.
How to prove it?
그것을 증명하는 방법?
By pleasing everyone?
모두를 기쁘게 함으로써?
I admit,
인정해요
I can't suddenly become someone
갑자기 누군가가 될 수는 없어
who ignores others' opinions
다른 사람의 의견을 무시하는 사람
and lays down the law.
그리고 법을 정합니다.
But that might not be the only way
하지만 그게 유일한 방법은 아닐 수도 있어요
to be a good forewoman.
좋은 여주인공이 되려면.
I just want to find a way that suits me.
그냥 나에게 맞는 방법을 찾고 싶을 뿐이에요.
Let me give you some advice.
몇 가지 조언을 드리겠습니다.
Before you've fully
완전히
established your authority,
당신의 권위를 확립했어요,
rumors like people saying
사람들이 말하는 것과 같은 소문
you got here through connections
넌 인맥을 통해 여기까지 왔어
aren't entirely bad.
완전히 나쁘지는 않습니다.
It all depends on how you use them—
그것은 모두 당신이 그것을 어떻게 사용하느냐에 달려 있습니다.
handled well, they can actually work to your advantage.
잘 처리하면 실제로 그렇게 할 수 있습니다 당신에게 유리하게 일하십시오.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Keep it up.
계속하세요.
According to Article 47
제47조에 따라
of the Purong Hotel Quality Management Rewards and Penalties Policy,
푸롱호텔 품질경영팀장 보상 및 처벌 정책,
[Purong Hotel]
[푸롱 호텔]
if management is negligent,
관리가 소홀하면
dereliction of duty,
직무유기,
and command errors
및 명령 오류
that cause the hotel
그게 호텔의 원인이었어
serious financial and reputational losses,
심각한 재정 및 평판 손실
they shall face severe disciplinary action,
그들은 직면하게 될 것이다 엄중한 징계 조치,
including demotion or removal from their position.
강등을 포함하여 또는 그 자리에서 제거됩니다.
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
do you want me
나를 원해
to bear such a big responsibility alone?
혼자서 그렇게 큰 책임을 져야 하나?
I'm just a junior HSKP Department manager.
난 그냥 후배야 HSKP 부서 관리자.
I can't take on such a big responsibility.
나는 그런 큰 책임을 질 수 없다.
This large-scale linen replacement alone
이 대규모 리넨 교체만으로도
comes with a cost difference of over a million just from the turnover.
이상의 비용 차이가 발생합니다. 매출액에서 백만 달러.
On top of that, there are the PR crisis media expenses,
그 외에도 다음이 있습니다. 홍보 위기 미디어 비용,
the costs of the complimentary stay promotions,
비용 무료 숙박 프로모션,
and the contract fees for switching laundry vendors.
그리고 계약금은 세탁업체 전환을 위해.
[Purong Hotel]
[푸롱 호텔]
HSKP Department
HSKP 부서
is tied to a huge portion of the hotel's revenue and cash flow.
큰 부분에 묶여있습니다 호텔의 수익과 현금 흐름에 대한 정보입니다.
You know that.
당신은 그것을 알고 있습니다.
I...
나는...
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
don't scare Mr. Feng.
Feng씨를 놀라게 하지 마세요.
Anyone hearing this might think you're about to audit him down to the last penny.
이 말을 듣는 사람은 당신이 이렇게 생각할 수도 있습니다. 그를 마지막 한 푼까지 감사하려고 합니다.
Besides, if the books aren't settled by year-end,
게다가 책이라면 연말까지 정산되지 않아
you can't really tell profit from loss anyway,
당신은 정말로 말할 수 없습니다 어쨌든 손실로 이익을 얻으세요
right?
오른쪽?
We know
우리는 알아요
you've just taken office,
방금 취임하셨군요,
so you're sweeping clean.
그래서 당신은 깨끗하게 청소하고 있습니다.
We all understand.
우리 모두는 이해합니다.
But
하지만
we do hope you can also
당신도 할 수 있기를 바랍니다
appreciate how difficult things are for those of us working under you.
얼마나 어려운 일인지 감사해 당신 밑에서 일하는 사람들을 위한 것입니다.
Some things
몇 가지
may sound easy to say,
말하기는 쉽지만
but they're not nearly as simple to carry out.
하지만 거의 다 됐어 수행하기가 간단합니다.
It is inevitable to make mistakes at work.
직장에서 실수를 하는 것은 불가피합니다.
Please go easy on us, Mr. Ji.
편하게 지내주세요, 지 선생님.
Yeah.
응.
If we strictly
엄밀히 말하면
follow the rules,
규칙을 따르세요
none of us will make any money.
우리 중 누구도 돈을 벌 수 없습니다.
You might as well
당신도 그럴 수도 있어요
just fine us all.
우리 모두 괜찮습니다.
Fine.
괜찮은.
I respect everyone's opinion.
나는 모든 사람의 의견을 존중합니다.
Then keep your position as Director Feng
그럼 Feng 국장직을 유지하세요
but his quarterly bonus will be deducted.
하지만 분기별 보너스는 공제됩니다.
He'll be given a major demerit
그 사람은 큰 불이익을 받게 될 거야
and a hotel-wide criticism.
그리고 호텔 전체의 비판.
Any objections?
이의가 있으신가요?
I scheduled a shift for you,
내가 당신을 위한 교대근무를 예약했어요
and you're being picky?
그런데 당신은 까다롭나요?
Do I have to beg you to work?
일하라고 구걸해야 하나요?
Director, I really can't work the night shift today.
감독님, 정말 못해요 오늘은 야간 근무를 해라.
If you can't work, then get out!
일할 수 없다면 나가라!
Get as far away as possible!
최대한 멀리 떠나세요!
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
What are you staring at?
당신은 무엇을 쳐다보고 있습니까?
Don't you know me?
당신은 나를 모르나요?
If you're not eating, get out!
안 먹을 거면 나가!
What kind of crappy food is this?
이게 무슨 형편없는 음식이냐?
I'm not eating!
난 안 먹어요!
What are you looking at?
무엇을 보고 있나요?
Just eat!
그냥 먹어!
Is that drunkard Feng crazy?
저 술고래 펑 미친거 아니냐?
Why is he yelling at everyone?
왜 그는 모두에게 소리를 지르는 걸까요?
Didn't you know?
몰랐나요?
Because of the bleach incident,
표백제 사건 때문에
he was publicly criticized by the whole hotel.
그는 공개적으로 비난을 받았다 호텔 전체에서.
The penalty is still posted on the official website.
페널티킥은 아직 남아있습니다 공식 홈페이지에서.
Everyone knows he's a parasite in the hotel.
다들 그 사람인 줄 알아요 호텔의 기생충.
Someone finally taught him a lesson.
누군가 마침내 그에게 교훈을 가르쳐주었습니다.
Then I must order a milk tea to celebrate today.
그럼 밀크티를 주문해야겠어요 오늘을 축하하기 위해.
Count me in.
나를 포함해 주세요.
From today on,
오늘부터
please have all departments follow the Purong Hotel service rules
모든 부서를 부탁드립니다 푸롱 호텔 서비스 규칙을 따르세요
to self-check for issues.
문제를 자체적으로 확인합니다.
[Purong Hotel]
[푸롱 호텔]
Strengthen management,
관리 강화,
upgrade basic employee training,
기본 직원 교육을 업그레이드하세요.
[Making guests feel at home]
[손님이 집에 있는 것처럼 느끼도록 만들기]
and conduct regular assessments.
정기적인 평가를 실시합니다.
Three receptionists must be on duty during off-peak hours.
접수원 3명이 근무해야 합니다. 피크가 아닌 시간 동안.
Other on-duty staff should make full use of their time
그 외 현직 직원 시간을 최대한 활용해야 해
[Convenience Handbook]
[편의 핸드북]
to improve foreign language skills
외국어 능력을 향상시키기 위해
and familiarize themselves with information around the hotel.
그리고 익숙해지세요 호텔 주변 정보와 함께
On-duty staff must keep hospitality etiquette in mind.
현직 직원이 지켜야 할 사항 환대 에티켓을 염두에 두세요.
Phones must be answered within three rings.
전화는 응답해야 합니다 세 개의 링 내에서.
Hello, Purong Hotel at your service.
안녕하세요 푸롱호텔입니다.
Yes, we do.
네, 그렇습니다.
The logistics department
물류부
is responsible for restoring Purong's tradition of displaying jasmine flowers.
푸롱의 복원을 담당하고 있습니다. 자스민 꽃을 전시하는 전통.
All areas must ensure to always provide
모든 영역에서는 항상
the best all-around experience for guests,
손님을 위한 최고의 종합 경험
including visual, olfactory, auditory, and tactile senses.
시각, 후각을 포함한 청각, 촉각.
I hope everyone in the hotel works together.
호텔에 있는 모든 사람들이 함께 일합니다.
Let's bring back the original intention of making guests feel at home
초심을 되찾자 손님들이 집처럼 편안함을 느낄 수 있게 만드는 것
to Purong.
푸롱에게.
Jia, are you done with your work?
지아야 일은 끝났어?
The guests in rooms 16, 17, and 18 have checked out.
16, 17, 18호실 투숙객 체크아웃했습니다.
Go and clean them up.
가서 청소하세요.
I have a headache.
두통이 있어요.
I think I'm sick.
내 생각엔 내가 아픈 것 같아.
Find someone else.
다른 사람을 찾으세요.
Yin Xiang.
인샹.
Stop right there, Miyu.
거기 멈춰라, 미유.
I still have a bunch of work to do.
아직 할 일이 많아요.
You can't just exploit me
나를 착취할 순 없어
because we're on good terms.
왜냐면 우리는 사이가 좋으니까.
Is anyone else free right now?
지금 시간이 있는 사람이 또 있나요?
Jia,
지아,
if you're not feeling well,
몸이 안 좋으면
go see a doctor.
의사를 만나러 가세요.
Bring back a doctor's note,
의사의 소견서를 가져와
and I'll let you go home to rest.
그리고 집에 가서 쉬도록 할게요.
Go now.
지금 가세요.
I got my period,
생리가 됐어,
and my stomach hurts.
그리고 배가 아파요.
You got your period twice in half a month?
한달에 두번씩 생리를 하셨나요?
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
Health is the most important thing.
건강이 가장 중요합니다.
If your body
몸이
can't handle the current workload,
현재 작업량을 처리할 수 없습니다.
that's okay.
괜찮아요.
Don't push yourself.
자신을 강요하지 마십시오.
I'll help you talk to HR.
HR 담당자와 통화할 수 있도록 도와드리겠습니다.
No need.
필요하지 않습니다.
It's not that serious.
그렇게 심각한 것은 아닙니다.
I feel much better now.
이제 기분이 훨씬 나아졌습니다.
Glad to hear that.
그 말을 들으니 기쁘군요.
If you can manage,
관리할 수 있다면
I'll still leave 16, 17, and 18 to you.
16, 17, 18은 아직 여러분에게 맡기겠습니다.
What's going on today?
오늘 무슨 일이야?
Why isn't she buying this anymore?
왜 그녀는 이것을 더 이상 사지 않는 걸까요?
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
You startled me!
당신은 나를 놀라게 했어요!
I wasn't doing anything.
나는 아무것도 하고 있지 않았다.
How could you just go through a guest's things?
어떻게 그냥 지나갈 수 있니? 손님의 물건?
I was just looking.
나는 단지 찾고 있었다.
I didn't take anything.
나는 아무것도 가져 가지 않았습니다.
Besides,
게다가,
this guest's belongings are scattered everywhere.
이 손님의 소지품 여기저기 흩어져있습니다.
How am I supposed to clean up if I can't touch them?
어떻게 청소해야 하나요? 내가 만질 수 없다면?
Is this what you call cleaning up?
이게 청소라고 하는 건가요?
You cleaned them right into the guest's bag.
당신은 그들을 청소했습니다 손님 가방에 바로 넣어요.
Is this fine now?
지금은 괜찮나요?
Jia, let me tell you,
지아, 말해주지
don't push your luck
행운을 빌지 마세요
to do these borderline things.
이런 경계선적인 일을 하려고요.
If something goes wrong,
문제가 발생하면
you won't even be able to explain yourself clearly.
넌 그럴 수조차 없을 거야 자신을 명확하게 설명하십시오.
I haven't finished yet.
아직 끝나지 않았어요.
Are you done?
끝났나요?
You've been targeting me since morning!
아침부터 나를 노리고 있었잖아!
Don't bully me too much!
나를 너무 괴롭히지 마세요!
I should be the one saying that.
나는 그런 말을 하는 사람이 되어야 한다.
Let me tell you, Jia.
말해주지, 지아.
It's fine if you have a problem with me.
나에게 문제가 있어도 괜찮습니다.
But as an attendant,
하지만 수행원으로서
you lead the other attendants
당신은 다른 참석자들을 이끌고
to slack off.
느슨해지기 위해.
Isn't this too much?
이건 너무한거 아냐?
Also,
또한,
please remember,
기억해 주세요
I am your forewoman,
나는 당신의 감독입니다
not your enemy.
당신의 적이 아닙니다.
I just checked Room 1818,
방금 1818호실을 확인했어요,
which you are responsible for.
당신이 담당하는 것입니다.
It's not cleaned up to standard.
표준에 맞게 정리되지 않았습니다.
After you finish cleaning this room,
이 방 청소를 마친 후에
go clean that one again.
가서 다시 청소해 보세요.
Who are you trying to scare?
누구에게 겁을 주려고 하는 겁니까?
Aren't you just a forewoman?
당신은 단지 부장 아닌가요?
So what if you're good at currying favor with management?
그러니까 네가 부탁을 잘하면 어쩌지? 관리로?
Let me tell you,
말해주지
if you want it cleaned, do it yourself.
청소하고 싶으면 직접 하세요.
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
can you carry it alone?
너 혼자 들고 다닐 수 있어?
Yes, I can.
예, 할 수 있습니다.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Hello, sir.
안녕하세요, 선생님.
Welcome to Purong Hotel.
푸롱 호텔에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
[Passport]
[여권]
I have a reservation.
예약이 있어요.
Excuse me, I was wondering
죄송합니다. 궁금해서요
if Amber Santos' installation exhibition
만약 앰버 산토스의 설치 전시
is around here?
이 근처에 있어?
Please wait a moment, sir.
잠시만 기다려 주십시오.
[Convenience Handbook]
[편의 핸드북]
I'm sorry, sir.
죄송합니다.
I don't really know.
나는 정말로 모른다.
It's fine.
괜찮습니다.
Are you looking for Amber Santos's
Amber Santos의
Four Seasons Art Exhibition?
를 찾고 계십니까? 사계절 미술전?
Yes, that's the one.
네, 그게 바로 그거예요.
This exhibition is indeed hard to find.
이번 전시는 정말 찾아보기 힘든데요.
It's in the art space on the eighth floor
8층 예술공간에 있어요
of the mall next door.
바로 옆 쇼핑몰.
There are posters up there.
거기에 포스터가 있어요.
You'll see them when you get up there.
거기 올라가면 그들을 볼 수 있을 거예요.
Just follow the directions.
그냥 지시를 따르십시오.
Okay, okay.
알았어, 알았어.
I've asked quite a few people,
꽤 많은 사람들에게 물어봤는데
and no one seems to know.
그리고 아무도 모르는 것 같아요.
This exhibition just opened in Shanghai,
이번 전시회는 상하이에서 막 열렸습니다.
so it's normal that many people don't know about it yet.
그래서 많은 사람들이 아직 그것에 대해 모른다.
But it should close at 7:30.
하지만 7시 30분에 문을 닫아야 해요.
Keep an eye on the time.
시간을 잘 확인하세요.
Don't miss it.
놓치지 마세요.
Okay, okay. Thank you.
알았어, 알았어. 감사합니다.
Glad to serve you.
당신을 섬기게 되어 기쁘네요.
Okay, thank you.
알겠습니다. 감사합니다.
Sir, it's done.
선생님, 다 됐어요.
-Thank you. -Enjoy your stay.
-감사합니다. - 즐거운 시간 보내세요.
Come in.
들어오세요.
Mr. Ji, the finance department is here to report the accounts.
재무부 지씨 계좌를 신고하러 왔습니다.
Let them in.
들여보내주세요.
Okay, come in.
좋아, 들어와.
Hello, Mr. Ji.
안녕하세요, 지씨.
I am the accounting manager of the finance department.
나는 회계 관리자입니다 재무부의.
My name is Gao Fan.
제 이름은 가오판이에요.
We received a notice this morning
오늘 아침에 통지를 받았습니다
saying that you want to check the accounts personally.
네가 하고 싶다고 말하면서 계좌를 개인적으로 확인해 보세요.
So,
그래서,
we dug out these ledgers
우리가 이 장부를 파냈어
for you from the warehouse.
당신을 위해 창고에서.
However,
그러나
there's a lot of dust on them,
먼지가 많아요
and the paper is quite brittle.
그리고 종이가 꽤 부서지기 쉽습니다.
When you flip through them later,
나중에 그 내용을 넘겨보면
please be very careful.
매우 조심하시기 바랍니다.
Where is your director?
감독님은 어디 계시나요?
You mean Director Huang?
황 감독 말인가요?
He went out early this morning with Mr. Wei to handle some business.
그는 오늘 아침 일찍 나갔다 업무를 처리하기 위해 웨이씨와 함께요.
He handed these matters over to me.
그는 이 문제를 나에게 넘겨주었다.
Look here.
여기를 보세요.
This cart
이 카트
mainly contains details of supply amounts,
주로 공급량에 대한 세부 정보가 포함되어 있습니다.
such as raw materials, consumables,
원자재, 소모품 등
semi-finished products, and warehouse goods.
반제품, 및 창고 물품.
You can
넌 할 수 있어
look through these freely.
자유롭게 살펴보세요.
This cart
이 카트
is all about
모든 것이
operating expenses and production costs.
운영비와 생산비.
This cart is a bit messy.
이 카트는 좀 지저분해요.
It mainly contains
주로
detailed ledgers of fixed assets,
고정 자산의 세부 원장,
three-column subsidiary ledgers for borrowing, lending, and balance,
3열 보조 원장 대출, 대출 및 잔액을 위해
and employee salary accounts.
직원 급여 계정.
That's enough.
그것으로 충분합니다.
Then I'll trouble you to review them personally, Mr. Ji.
그럼 내가 널 힘들게 할게 개인적으로 검토해 보도록 하겠습니다, 지 선생님.
Okay.
좋아요.
Mr. Gao,
가오 씨,
did you see Mr. Ji's face?
지씨 얼굴 봤어?
With all those carts of stuff,
그 많은 물건을 담은 카트를 가지고
if he doesn't get dizzy looking at them,
만약 그 사람이 그것들을 보고 현기증을 느끼지 않는다면,
he'll at least get a dust mite allergy.
그 사람은 최소한 집먼지 진드기 알레르기가 생길 거예요.
Didn't he want to investigate?
그 사람은 조사하고 싶지 않았나요?
Let him.
그를 보자.
Take his time to investigate it.
시간을 내어 조사해 보세요.
Why did you think of
왜
treating me to barbecue today?
를 생각했나요? 오늘 나한테 바비큐 대접해줄래?
I just care about you.
나는 단지 당신에게 관심이 있습니다.
How's the audit going?
감사는 어떻게 진행되고 있나요?
As for the audit,
감사에 관해서는
I originally thought
원래는
following the supply of linens
리넨 공급에 따라
and cleaning fees
및 청소비
could reveal some discrepancies.
약간의 불일치가 드러날 수 있습니다.
But the accounts are balanced,
하지만 계정은 균형을 이루고 있습니다.
the receipts are complete,
영수증이 완료되었습니다.
and there are no loopholes.
허점이 없습니다.
The finance department is like a spider's web.
재무부 거미줄과 같습니다.
They won't let someone who just arrived
방금 도착한 사람은 가만두지 않을 거야
find any flaws so easily.
너무 쉽게 결함을 찾아냅니다.
Rui,
루이,
stay and work with me.
여기 남아서 나와 함께 일해 보세요.
Help me.
도와주세요.
You think I'm not sincere enough?
내가 충분히 성실하지 않다고 생각하시나요?
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
Ji Feng,
지펑
stop drinking.
그만 마시세요.
Listen to me.
내 말을 들어보세요.
Actually, at this dinner today,
사실 오늘 저녁 식사에서는
I'm here to say goodbye.
나는 작별 인사를 하러 왔습니다.
I've already made arrangements
난 이미 준비를 다 했어
to go to Guilin to be a financial director.
계림으로 가다 재무 이사가 되려면.
By the way,
그런데,
before I leave,
떠나기 전에
I have a gift for you.
당신을 위한 선물이 있어요.
I hope it's useful.
유용하길 바랍니다.
This is the account book I kept when I was the head of accounting.
이건 내가 보관했던 장부야 제가 회계부장이었을 때요.
[F&B Department]
[F&B부]
[Handled by: Manager Chen] [Handled by: Manager Jia]
[담당자 : 첸 매니저] [담당자 : 지아 매니저]
The real accounts.
실제 계정.
Later, they found out.
나중에 그들은 알게 되었습니다.
My career hit the ceiling.
내 경력은 한계에 도달했습니다.
Now I am the daily audit supervisor.
이제 저는 일일 감사 감독관입니다.
But honestly I'm just a nobody
하지만 솔직히 난 아무 것도 아니야
drifting around in the finance department.
재무부서에서 떠돌고 있어요.
I can understand how you feel.
나는 당신의 기분을 이해할 수 있습니다.
I've endured for so many years
나는 수년 동안 참아왔다
and my skills are completely gone.
그리고 내 실력이 완전히 사라졌어요.
I can't help you with anything.
나는 아무것도 당신을 도울 수 없습니다.
The little useful information I have left
내가 남긴 작은 유용한 정보
has all been given to you.
모든 것이 당신에게 주어졌습니다.
Rui,
루이,
here's to you.
여기 당신에게 있습니다.
May your career take off
당신의 경력이 시작되기를 바랍니다
and everything go your way.
모든 것이 원하는 대로 진행됩니다.
Ji Feng,
지펑
I'm ashamed
부끄러워요
I left you behind to handle everything alone
나는 당신을 뒤에 남겨두고 모든 걸 혼자 처리해야 해
while I ran off like a deserter.
나는 탈영병처럼 도망쳤다.
I'll drink three glasses as a penalty.
벌칙으로 세 잔을 마시겠습니다.
Rui,
루이,
you don't owe me anything.
당신은 나에게 빚진 것이 없습니다.
You have your future,
당신에게는 미래가 있습니다.
and I have my challenges.
그리고 나에게는 도전이 있습니다.
We are going our separate ways.
우리는 각자의 길을 가고 있습니다.
It's just a pity.
안타깝습니다.
Why feel guilty?
왜 죄책감을 느끼는가?
No matter what,
무슨 일이 있어도
seeing you find your place
네가 네 자리를 찾는 걸 보니
makes me happy.
나를 행복하게 해준다.
Really.
정말.
Cheers.
건배.
Mr. Tan, time for your medicine.
탄 씨, 약을 드실 시간이에요.
What do you always call me
넌 항상 나를 뭐라고 부르지
"Mr. Tan"?
"탄 씨"?
Call me Daniel from now on.
이제부터 다니엘이라고 불러주세요.
You're making me sound old.
당신은 나를 늙어 보이게 만들고 있어요.
Daniel, here you go.
다니엘, 여기요.
Just leave it there.
그냥 거기에 두세요.
You still have to take it if I leave it here.
아직도 가져가야 해 여기에 놔두면.
You can't skip a single dose.
단일 복용량을 건너뛸 수 없습니다.
You don't want to take your medicine again?
당신은 원하지 않습니다 또 약을 먹어?
Fine.
괜찮은.
I'll call Jizhou right now
지금 당장 Jizhou에 전화할게
and have him take you back.
그 사람이 당신을 다시 데려가도록 하세요.
Eat, eat, eat.
먹고, 먹고, 먹습니다.
Don't ever mention
절대 언급하지 마세요
Jizhou taking me back again.
나를 다시 데려가는 Jizhou.
Swallow it.
그것을 삼켜라.
Do you often meet guests like this?
이런 손님 자주 만나시나요?
So disobedient.
너무 불순종합니다.
No.
아니요.
Mr. Tan is very easy to get along with.
Tan 씨는 사이가 매우 좋습니다.
Are you busy on the executive floor?
임원층에서 바쁘신가요?
Is the forewoman job going well?
부장 일은 잘 되고 있나요?
I'm working very well here.
나는 여기서 아주 잘 일하고 있어요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
You guys talk.
너희들은 얘기한다.
I'll get going.
나는 갈 것이다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Good girl.
좋은 여자.
We meet again.
우리는 다시 만난다.
It's you?
당신인가요?
I'm looking for Daniel.
나는 다니엘을 찾고 있어요.
I'm Tan Jiaming, his son.
저는 그의 아들 Tan Jiaming입니다.
Come in.
들어오세요.
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Auntie Wanjun is here too.
완준 아줌마도 왔어요.
Ms. Xu.
쉬 씨.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
This exhibition is very nice.
이번 전시 참 좋네요.
But what I'm more grateful for is
하지만 내가 더 감사한 것은
that you saved my father's life.
당신이 내 아버지의 생명을 구했다고요.
So this is a little token of my appreciation.
그래서 이것은 작은 토큰입니다 내 감사의 말.
I hope you can accept it.
당신이 그것을 받아들일 수 있기를 바랍니다.
[Amber Santos Four Seasons Art Exhibition]
[앰버 산토스 사계절 미술전]
I can't accept it.
나는 그것을 받아들일 수 없다.
No, you must accept it.
아니, 받아들여야 합니다.
I am really grateful to you.
정말 감사드립니다.
I've never seen my father so happy.
나는 아버지가 그토록 기뻐하시는 것을 본 적이 없습니다.
It's all thanks to you.
모두 당신 덕분이에요.
Mr. Tan,
탄 씨,
I appreciate your kindness,
당신의 친절에 감사드립니다.
But I really can't accept the gift.
그런데 정말 그 선물을 받을 수가 없어요.
If you are really satisfied with my service,
정말 만족하신다면 내 서비스,
then you are welcome to visit Purong Hotel more often.
그럼 천만에요 푸롱 호텔을 더 자주 방문하세요.
All right.
괜찮은.
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
you're really different.
당신은 정말 달라요.
Here's the thing.
여기에 문제가 있습니다.
When I chat with my father,
아버지와 이야기를 나눌 때
he often mentions you.
그는 당신을 자주 언급합니다.
He said "Ms. Xu who takes care of me
그는 "나를 보살펴주는 쉬씨
studied hotel management,
호텔 경영학을 전공했지만
but she has a great sense of art.
예술 감각이 뛰어나다.
It's a pleasure to talk with her."
대화를 나눌 수 있어서 즐겁다"고 말했다.
Seeing you today,
오늘 뵙겠습니다
I can see that's true.
나는 그것이 사실임을 알 수 있다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Ms. Xu, can I ask you a question?
Xu 씨, 질문 하나 해도 될까요?
Why do you work as an attendant at Purong?
왜 푸롱에서 승무원으로 일하시나요?
I...
나는...
I'm not trying to pry into your privacy.
나는 당신의 사생활을 캐내려는 것이 아닙니다.
It's like this.
이렇습니다.
I think with your knowledge and ability,
나는 당신의 지식과 능력을 생각합니다
you should go to a bigger platform
더 큰 플랫폼으로 가야 해
to do work that better reflects your personal value.
더 잘 반영하는 일을 하기 위해 당신의 개인적인 가치.
So,
그래서,
this is my name card.
이건 내 이름표야.
If you need it,
필요하다면
[Curator, Tan Jizhou]
[큐레이터 탄지저우]
I can help you find work
네가 일자리를 찾는 걸 도와줄 수 있어
related to the arts,
예술과 관련된
and I'd be willing to recommend you as well.
그리고 난 기꺼이 그럴 거야 당신도 추천해요.
You are a curator?
당신은 큐레이터입니까?
That's amazing.
정말 놀랍습니다.
Do you know me?
저를 아시나요?
Then I guess I'm not amazing enough.
그렇다면 나는 충분히 놀라운 사람이 아닌 것 같다.
Well, Mr. Tan,
음, 탄 선생님,
thank you for acknowledging me.
나를 인정해주셔서 감사합니다.
But I currently have no plans
하지만 현재는 계획이 없어요
to leave Purong.
푸롱을 떠나려고.
Because I think
내 생각엔
being able to provide every guest away from home
제공할 수 있어서 집에 없는 모든 손님
with a service that feels like home
집처럼 편안한 서비스로
is a very valuable thing.
매우 귀중한 일입니다.
So I really love my current job.
그래서 나는 지금의 일을 정말 좋아한다.
Okay.
좋아요.
I understand.
이해합니다.
If you need anything,
필요한 것이 있으면
you can contact me anytime.
언제든지 저에게 연락하실 수 있습니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Mr. Tan, good night.
탄 씨, 잘 자요.
Good night.
안녕히 주무세요.
Mr. Ji.
지 씨.
You...
당신은...
What's wrong with you?
왜 그래?
Nothing.
아무것도 아님.
I just had a little drink.
방금 술을 조금 마셨어요.
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
I'm fine.
잘 지내요.
I have the room card.
객실 카드가 있어요.
Let me swipe it for you.
스와이프해 보겠습니다.
Please come in.
들어오세요.
Xu Miyu,
쉬 미유,
thank you
감사합니다
for staying.
머물기 위해.
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
It's okay.
괜찮아요.
I can handle it.
나는 그것을 처리할 수 있다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
[Zhao Ning – 19th Floor, Rest] [He Xiao – 19th Floor, Night Shift]
[자오닝 – 19층, 휴식] [허샤오 – 19층 야간 근무]
Ms. Xu.
쉬 씨.
Ms. Xu, are you there?
쉬 씨, 거기 계세요?
Yes.
예.
Come quickly.
빨리 오세요.
Jia has been held up by the guest
손님이 지아를 붙잡았습니다
in room 1817.
1817호실에 있어요.
I'm coming.
나는 간다.
Ke Wenxue,
케 웬슈에,
do you have the information of the guest in room 1817?
당신은 정보를 가지고 있습니까? 1817호실 손님의 말인가요?
She's a middle-aged female guest.
중년 여성 손님입니다.
It seems she was upgraded from the regular floor.
업그레이드 된 것 같아요 일반 층에서.
Okay, got it, thanks.
알겠습니다. 감사합니다.
Hello, sorry to bother you.
안녕하세요, 귀찮게 해서 죄송합니다.
I am the forewoman of the executive floor.
저는 집행층의 주임입니다.
May I come in?
들어가도 될까요?
Come in!
들어오세요!
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
We have received your complaint.
귀하의 불만사항이 접수되었습니다.
I'm here to understand the situation.
나는 상황을 이해하기 위해 여기에 왔습니다.
Ask her.
그녀에게 물어보세요.
I didn't take it.
나는 그것을 받아들이지 않았습니다.
You're lying!
당신은 거짓말을하고 있습니다!
Hand over my diamond ring right now!
지금 당장 내 다이아몬드 반지를 넘겨주세요!
I didn't take her diamond ring.
나는 그녀의 다이아몬드 반지를 가져가지 않았습니다.
I really didn't!
난 정말 안 그랬어!
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
I am the general manager here.
제가 이곳의 총책임자입니다.
May I come in?
들어가도 될까요?
Come in.
들어오세요.
This customer said
이 고객은
she lost a diamond ring in her room.
그녀는 방에서 다이아몬드 반지를 잃어버렸습니다.
She took it!
그녀가 가져갔어!
Look at how sneaky she is.
그녀가 얼마나 교활한지보세요.
You were about to run as soon as I walked in.
너 달려갈 뻔 했어 들어오자마자.
Why did you run?
왜 달렸나요?
I had just finished cleaning the room and was about to leave.
나는 방금 방 청소를 마쳤다. 그리고 떠나려고 했어요.
Have you finished cleaning the room?
방 청소는 다 마쳤나요?
Have you made the bed?
침대는 정돈하셨나요?
You even left your rag in the room.
당신은 심지어 걸레를 방에 남겨 두었습니다.
If you didn't do anything wrong,
아무 잘못도 하지 않았다면
why were you panicking?
왜 당황했어?
When I entered the room,
내가 방에 들어갔을 때
I lost my diamond ring.
다이아몬드 반지를 잃어버렸어요.
Please calm down first.
먼저 진정하세요.
We will investigate this thoroughly,
우리는 이 문제를 철저히 조사할 것입니다.
and then...
그리고...
Mr. Ji.
지 씨.
I have really checked this room.
나는 이 방을 실제로 확인해 보았다.
Madam, I apologize
부인, 사과드립니다
for your unpleasant experience.
당신의 불쾌한 경험을 위해.
May I ask how long after the attendant left
언제까지인지 물어봐도 될까요? 수행원이 떠난 후
did you call her back?
그 사람한테 다시 전화했어?
As soon as I noticed something wrong with her,
뭔가 눈치채자마자 그 사람이 틀렸어,
I checked my bag.
나는 내 가방을 확인했다.
The diamond ring was indeed missing,
다이아몬드 반지는 실제로 없어졌습니다.
so I went out to find her immediately.
그래서 나는 즉시 그녀를 찾으러 나갔다.
Hand it over right now.
지금 당장 넘겨주세요.
I didn't take it.
나는 그것을 받아들이지 않았습니다.
Jia,
지아,
come in and check with me.
들어와서 나한테 확인해봐.
Excuse me, wait a moment.
죄송합니다. 잠시만 기다려주세요.
Alright.
괜찮은.
Let me ask you,
물어볼게
did you take the guest's belongings or not?
당신은 가져갔나요? 손님의 소지품인가요?
If you don't tell me the truth,
나에게 진실을 말하지 않으면
I really can't help you.
나는 정말로 당신을 도울 수 없습니다.
I was just curious
그냥 궁금해서
and searched the price online.
그리고 온라인으로 가격을 검색해 봤습니다.
[Moissanite Ring – 18K Gold Engagement Diamond Ring, High-End Replica Ring]
[모이사나이트 반지 - 18K 골드 약혼 다이아몬드반지, 고급레플리카반지]
[True Love Lab-Grown Gemstone Ring]
[진정한 사랑 실험실에서 자란 보석 반지]
[High-Quality 18K Gold Six-Prong Lab Diamond Ring]
[고급 18K 골드 Six-Prong Lab 다이아몬드 반지]
You rummaged through the guest's bag again?
뒤져보셨는데요 손님 가방 또?
Okay.
좋아요.
Come with me and turn yourself in.
나와 함께 가서 제출하세요.
Sister Miyu,
미유 자매님,
I was wrong.
나는 틀렸다.
I really was wrong.
나는 정말로 틀렸다.
Please, listen to my explanation.
제 설명을 들어주세요.
I thought
내 생각엔
it was just a small matter.
그것은 단지 작은 문제였습니다.
[Search for Similar Items]
[유사상품 검색]
[Moissanite– Birthday Gift for Girlfriend]
[모이사나이트- 여자친구 생일 선물]
I wouldn't want it
나는 그것을 원하지 않을 것이다
[S990 sterling silver little snake ring]
[S990 스털링 실버 작은 뱀 반지]
[Minimalist sterling silver tail ring for men and women]
[미니멀리스트 스털링 실버 테일링 남성 및 여성용]
even if she gave it to me.
비록 그녀가 그것을 나에게 주었다고 해도.
I knew it was a fake.
나는 그것이 가짜라는 것을 알았습니다.
But it was just such a coincidence.
그러나 그것은 단지 우연의 일치였습니다.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Not making a sound,
소리가 나지 않아
you scared me!
너 나한테 겁줬어!
Sorry. Sorry.
죄송합니다. 죄송합니다.
I realized right then that something was wrong.
나는 그제서야 깨달았다 뭔가 잘못됐어요.
Fortunately, I caught her.
다행히 나는 그녀를 잡았습니다.
I...
나는...
Our staff will be right here.
우리 직원이 바로 여기 있을 거예요.
Please wait a moment.
잠시만 기다려주세요.
It's over.
끝났습니다.
She's going to get sued.
그녀는 고소당할 거예요.
She deserves it.
그녀는 그럴 자격이 있습니다.
If she's got sticky fingers, she shouldn't be working as an attendant.
그녀의 손가락이 끈적끈적하다면, 그 사람은 도우미로 일하면 안 돼요.
Is this your first day knowing Jia?
오늘이 Jia를 처음 알게 된 날인가요?
She only acts tough on the outside.
그녀는 겉으로만 거친 행동을 한다.
She doesn't have the guts to steal.
그녀는 훔칠 용기가 없습니다.
How long do I have to wait?
얼마나 기다려야 하나요?
Can you hurry up?
서둘러 주실 수 있나요?
I don't know if our forewoman
우리 감독이
can settle this.
이것을 해결할 수 있습니다.
Jia and Ms. Xu fell out a long time ago.
Jia와 Ms. Xu는 오래 전에 사이가 나빠졌습니다.
I'm afraid no one can save her this time.
이번에는 누구도 그녀를 구할 수 없을까 두렵습니다.
It's hard to say if Ms. Xu can even save herself.
Ms. Xu가 맞는지 말하기는 어렵습니다. 심지어 자신을 구할 수도 있습니다.
Mr. Ji just took office,
지씨가 막 취임했어요
and this scandal happens on the executive floor.
그리고 이번 스캔들 임원 층에서 발생합니다.
This is a huge embarrassment for him.
이것은 그에게 커다란 당혹감이다.
Even with Ms. Xu‘s strong backing,
Xu 씨의 강력한 지원에도 불구하고
she probably won't
아마 그렇지 않을 것 같아
escape the blame this time.
이번엔 비난에서 벗어나세요.
Stop looking.
그만 찾아보세요.
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
You can't just favor your own employees.
직원들만 편애할 수는 없습니다.
I told you she took it.
나는 그녀가 그것을 가져 갔다고 말했다.
Why do you insist on searching the room?
왜 굳이 방을 수색하려고 합니까?
Ma'am,
부인,
the situation is still unclear.
상황은 아직 불분명하다.
It might just be a misunderstanding.
단지 오해일 수도 있습니다.
What's wrong with this toilet?
이 화장실에 무슨 문제가 있나요?
Dare.
도전.
This toilet has been clogged for ages.
이 화장실은 오랫동안 막혀 있었습니다.
The water won't go down at all.
물이 전혀 내려가지 않습니다.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
I asked you to find my stuff.
내 물건을 찾아달라고 부탁했어요.
Why are you plunging the toilet?
왜 변기에 물을 빠뜨리는 걸까요?
Go.
가다.
Mr. Ji, the security footage you asked for is ready.
지 씨, 보안 영상 요청하신 내용이 준비되었습니다.
Mr. Ji, we didn't find the ring.
지 선생님, 반지를 못 찾았어요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Ma'am,
부인,
I need to go to the surveillance room.
감시실로 가야 해요.
You can't just leave.
그냥 떠날 수는 없습니다.
Are you trying to stall me?
나를 방해하려고 하는 건가요?
Get this straight.
이것을 똑바로 이해하십시오.
I'm making things easier for you now.
이제 나는 당신을 위해 일을 더 쉽게 만들고 있습니다.
Problems that can be solved with money
돈으로 해결할 수 있는 문제
aren't really problems,
별로 문제가 되지 않아
right?
오른쪽?
I didn't want to make a big deal out of this.
나는 원하지 않았다 이것으로 큰 일을 해내십시오.
It's very bad for your hotel's image.
호텔 이미지에 매우 나쁜 영향을 미칩니다.
But if you insist on beating around the bush,
하지만 고집한다면 덤불 주위를 두들겨 패며
I'll have to call the police.
경찰에 전화해야겠어요
Two hours.
2시간.
Give us another two hours.
두 시간만 더 주세요.
We will definitely find it.
우리는 반드시 찾아낼 것입니다.
I don't have two hours.
나에겐 두 시간이 없다.
I'm checking out.
체크아웃 중이에요.
One hour.
1시간.
Alright.
괜찮은.
Just one hour.
딱 한 시간만요.
[Notice of calling the fire police]
[소방서 출동 안내]
Mr. Ji.
지 씨.
Instead of looking for the ring,
반지를 찾는 대신
why are you following me?
왜 나를 따라오는 거야?
That ring is fake.
그 반지는 가짜예요.
Evidence.
증거.
Jia...
지아...
I judged from the guest's attitude.
나는 손님의 태도로 판단했다.
Normally, if someone loses something so valuable,
일반적으로 누군가가 패배하면 정말 귀중한 것
they would want to know the truth
그들은 진실을 알고 싶어할 거야
instead of just asking for compensation.
단순히 보상을 요구하는 것보다.
However,
그러나
a 100,000 yuan ring disappears,
10만 위안짜리 반지가 사라졌어요,
and she doesn't care how it got lost.
그리고 그녀는 그것이 어떻게 분실되었는지 상관하지 않습니다.
She just opens her mouth and asks for money.
그 사람은 그냥 입을 열어요 그리고 돈을 요구합니다.
I think it's very suspicious.
제 생각에는 매우 의심스럽습니다.
At a time like this, you're still trying to shield your staff.
이런 때, 당신은 여전히 직원을 보호하려고 노력하고 있습니다.
When you run into a guest who frames you like this,
손님을 만났을 때 누가 널 이렇게 액자에 넣어놨어?
the only solution is…
유일한 해결책은…
To find what she's hiding.
그녀가 무엇을 숨기고 있는지 찾으려면.
You have 50 minutes left.
50분 남았습니다.
If you can't find the ring, you pay.
반지를 찾을 수 없으면 비용을 지불하세요.
Me?
나?
Why should I pay?
왜 지불해야 합니까?
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
I told you to look for something.
내가 뭐 좀 찾아보라고 했잖아.
Why are you digging in the toilet?
왜 화장실을 파고 있는 걸까요?
You all know how much
다들 얼마인지 아시죠
a one-carat diamond costs.
1캐럿 다이아몬드의 가격.
A random brand costs over 100,000.
무작위 브랜드의 가격은 100,000이 넘습니다.
I won't argue with you.
나는 당신과 논쟁하지 않을 것입니다.
Let's round it off
마무리해보자
and just pay me 100,000.
그리고 그냥 100,000원만 줘.
Now you're the ones making trouble for me?
지금 나한테 문제를 일으키고 있는 게 너야?
What terrible luck.
정말 끔찍한 행운이군요.
I'm going to the lobby to check out.
체크아웃하러 로비로 가볼게요.
Call your general manager here!
여기로 총책임자에게 전화하세요!
Ma'am.
부인.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
I'm checking out.
체크아웃 중이에요.
Ma'am,
부인,
your ring hasn't been found yet, right?
네 반지는 아직 못 찾았지?
I brought a professional here
여기 전문가를 데려왔어
to help you look for it.
당신이 그것을 찾는 데 도움이됩니다.
Please give us two more minutes.
2분만 더 시간을 주세요.
You look for it.
당신은 그것을 찾습니다.
I'm leaving.
나는 떠난다.
This way, please.
이쪽으로 부탁드립니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Miss.
미스
I can't take this toilet apart.
이 화장실은 분해할 수 없어요.
They were all installed by the manufacturer.
모두 설치되어 있었어요 제조업체에 의해.
If you want it removed, the Engineering Department has to follow the procedure.
제거를 원하시면, 엔지니어링 부서 절차를 따라야 합니다.
I can fill out any paperwork you need later.
어떤 서류라도 작성할 수 있어요 나중에 필요합니다.
Can we just fix this emergency first?
이 긴급상황을 먼저 해결할 수 있을까요?
No.
아니요.
Call me when you have all the paperwork.
서류가 다 준비되면 전화주세요.
All talk and no action again.
모든 말만 하고 다시는 행동하지 않습니다.
Does your hotel
당신의 호텔은
only play these childish games?
이런 유치한 게임만 하는 거야?
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
Coming through.
통과합니다.
Rumors like people saying you got here
사람들이 당신이 여기에 왔다고 말하는 것과 같은 소문이 돌고 있어요
through connections aren't entirely a bad thing.
연결을 통해 완전히 나쁜 것은 아닙니다.
If you handled well, they can actually work to your advantage.
당신이 잘 처리했다면 그들은 실제로 당신에게 유리하게 일하십시오.
Sir.
선생님.
Wait a moment.
잠시만 기다려주세요.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Don't you know me?
당신은 나를 모르나요?
I'm the new forewoman
내가 새로운 감독이야
promoted by Mr. Ji.
지씨가 홍보한 거야.
If you want to follow the procedure,
절차를 따르려면
how about this?
이건 어때?
I'll call him right now
지금 바로 전화할게
and have him personally do the paperwork for you?
그리고 그 사람을 개인적으로 데려가세요 당신을 위해 서류 작업을 해주시나요?
Okay, okay.
알았어, 알았어.
It's disassembled.
분해된 상태입니다.
If you're done,
다 마쳤으면
you call me.
당신이 나에게 전화.
Ms. Wang,
왕 선생님,
-please wait outside. -I'm just looking.
-밖에서 기다려주세요. - 그냥 보고 있어요.
It smells bad here.
여기서는 냄새가 안 좋아요.
Sorry for the trouble.
불편을 끼쳐드려 죄송합니다.
I've found it.
나는 그것을 찾았습니다.
This is a valuable item.
이것은 귀중한 품목입니다.
Our hotel needs to go through an appraisal process.
우리 호텔은 이 과정을 거쳐야 해 평가 과정.
Please wait a moment.
잠시만 기다려주세요.
Appraisal?
값 매김?
Mr. Zhu,
주 씨,
are you almost here?
거의 다 왔어?
There's no need for an appraisal.
평가는 필요없습니다.
Why go through all that trouble?
왜 그 모든 어려움을 겪어야 합니까?
No need, no need.
필요 없어, 필요 없어.
Are you sure?
확실합니까?
This is a diamond ring worth over 100,000.
10만 원이 넘는 다이아몬드 반지입니다.
Our hotel absolutely cannot take this lightly.
저희 호텔은 절대 이것을 가볍게 여길 수는 없습니다.
I'm sure.
나는 확신한다.
What appraisal?
무슨 평가요?
You are so much trouble.
당신은 정말 문제가 많습니다.
Is there anything else I can help you with?
다른 건 없나요? 제가 도와드릴까요?
We look forward to seeing you again at Purong Hotel.
우리는 당신을 다시 만나기를 기대합니다 푸롱 호텔에서.
We are always at your service!
우리는 항상 귀하의 서비스에 있습니다!
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
drink some more honey water,
꿀물 좀 더 마셔
and eat some apples and oranges to sober up.
그리고 사과 좀 먹어 그리고 기분전환용 오렌지.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
About that jewelry appraisal...
그 보석 감정에 대해서...
There's no jewelry appraisal.
보석 감정은 없습니다.
I was bluffing.
나는 허세를 부리고 있었다.
She knew her stuff was fake,
그녀는 자신의 물건이 가짜라는 것을 알았습니다.
so she wouldn't dare to drag it out.
그래서 그녀는 감히 그것을 끌어낼 수 없었습니다.
Miyu,
미유,
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
All right.
괜찮은.
Just learn your lesson
교훈을 얻으세요
and don't do it again.
그리고 다시는 그러지 마세요.
Go wash your face.
가서 세수하세요.
As service staff on the executive floor,
Executive Floor의 서비스 직원으로서
our behavior
우리의 행동
represents the service level of Purong Hotel.
서비스 수준을 나타냅니다. 푸롱 호텔의 모습입니다.
In this incident, Jia violated
이 사건에서 지아는
Puyong Hotel's HSKP Department,
부용호텔 HSKP부
Article 27,
제27조,
by privately inspecting
개인적으로 검사하여
a guest's personal belongings.
손님의 개인 소지품.
After a joint decision by the HSKP Department and HR Department,
공동의결을 거쳐 HSKP 부서 및 HR 부서,
your monthly bonus will be deducted.
월별 보너스가 공제됩니다.
Do you accept this?
이것을 받아들이십니까?
I accept.
동의합니다.
I hope this incident
이 사건이 일어나길 바라요
will serve as a warning to everyone.
모든 사람에게 경고가 될 것입니다.
Don't think that
그렇게 생각하지 마세요
being late,
늦었어
gossiping about guests,
손님에 대해 험담을 하고 있어
slacking off, faking an illness,
태만함, 병인 척
slipping away, or skipping work
빠져나가거나 일을 빼먹는 중
won't cause problems just because no one sees you.
문제를 일으키지 않을 것이다 단지 아무도 당신을 보지 못하기 때문입니다.
I'm not doing this to make things difficult for anyone,
난 이러지 않을 거야 누구에게나 일을 어렵게 만들려고
but to help everyone avoid risks together.
하지만 모두가 함께 위험을 피할 수 있도록 돕기 위해서입니다.
Workplace competition is certainly fierce,
직장 내 경쟁은 확실히 치열해요,
but it's more about
하지만 그것은
cooperation and mutual benefit.
에 관한 것입니다. 협력과 상호 이익.
I may not be your friend,
난 네 친구가 아닐 수도 있어,
but
하지만
I am at least your partner.
나는 적어도 당신의 파트너입니다.
As the forewoman,
감독으로서
I hope whenever you have any difficulties,
어려움이 있을 때마다
you can come to me.
당신은 나에게 올 수 있습니다.
I will spare no effort
노력을 아끼지 않겠습니다
to help everyone accomplish our tasks together.
모두를 돕기 위해 우리의 임무를 함께 완수하세요.
There is only one goal.
목표는 하나뿐입니다.
I hope everyone can do their part
모두가 자신의 역할을 다할 수 있기를 바랍니다
to improve the service on the executive floor together.
서비스를 개선하기 위해 이그제큐티브 플로어에서 함께요.
All right?
괜찮은?
Yes.
예.
[Wishing you prosperity and good fortune]
[귀하의 번영과 행운을 기원합니다]
Miyu sent a really big red packet.
미유가 정말 큰 빨간 패킷을 보냈어요.
What does this mean?
이것은 무엇을 의미합니까?
Penalties must be given,
페널티가 주어져야 합니다.
but compensations must also be made.
하지만 보상도 이루어져야 합니다.
This is everyone's overtime pay from last time.
이건 모두의 초과 근무 수당이야 지난번부터.
Although it's still less than what you deserve.
아직은 덜하긴 하지만 당신이 마땅히 받아야 할 것보다.
I thought the overtime pay wasn't approved.
초과근무 수당이라고 생각했는데 승인되지 않았습니다.
Are you paying out of your own pocket?
당신은 당신의 주머니에서 돈을 지불하고 있습니까?
My bonus from last time
지난번 보너스
is completely gone.
완전히 사라졌습니다.
If you guys go against me again,
너희들이 또 나한테 반항하면
I'll have nothing to eat.
나는 먹을 것이 아무것도 없을 것이다.
Rooms 1805 and 1807 are checking out.
1805호와 1807호가 체크아웃 중입니다.
Copy that.
복사하세요.
Alright.
괜찮은.
Let's get to work.
일하러 가자.
Xu Miyu,
쉬 미유,
you can do this.
당신은 이것을 할 수 있습니다.
You can be a good forewoman,
당신은 훌륭한 감독이 될 수 있어요
and do this job well.
그리고 이 일을 잘 하세요.
You can rely on yourself,
당신은 스스로를 의지할 수 있어요,
and live every day of your life well.
그리고 매일매일을 잘 살아라.
[Purong Hotel]
[푸롱 호텔]
Mr. Qian.
치안 씨.
Mr. Ji.
지 씨.
Have a seat.
앉으세요.
This is the reservation cancellation form for Shijing Technology.
예약취소 안내입니다 Shijing Technology의 양식입니다.
Why was it canceled?
왜 취소되었나요?
They were already quite hesitant.
그들은 이미 상당히 주저하고 있었습니다.
Now,
이제,
with this whole bleach incident,
이번 표백제 사건으로 인해,
[Cancellation of Reservation Agreement]
[예약 동의 취소]
they are even more afraid to give such a big order
그들은 더욱 두려워한다 그렇게 큰 명령을 내리다니
[Party A (Seal): Shijing Technology Co., Ltd.]
[당사자 A(인감): Shijing Technology Co., Ltd.]
to us.
우리에게.
[Cancellation of Reservation Agreement]
[예약 동의 취소]
Zhanpeng Industry is an old client,
Zhanpeng Industry는 오래된 고객입니다.
but they haven't renewed the contract.
하지만 그들은 계약을 갱신하지 않았습니다.
This is the written notice
이것은 서면 통지서입니다
we sent them a month in advance.
우리는 한 달 전에 미리 보냈어요.
Take a look.
보세요.
How did they reply?
그들은 어떻게 대답했습니까?
They just said they're still considering,
방금 아직 고려 중이라고 하더군요,
with no definite answer.
확실한 대답이 없습니다.
We also sent people over to visit,
우리는 또한 사람들을 방문하도록 보냈습니다.
but they either said the boss wasn't in
그런데 그 사람들이 사장님이 안에 없다고 했어
or gave vague answers.
아니면 막연한 대답을 하기도 했고요.
I figured,
내 생각엔,
since our agreement has expired,
우리의 계약이 만료되었기 때문에
this weekend I'll have
이번 주말에는
the front desk, housekeeping, and finance settle the accounts
프런트 데스크, 하우스키핑, 그리고 재정이 결산을 해
and take the rooms back.
그리고 방을 다시 가져가세요.